<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For The Crown – Crown Events</title>
    <link>/wiki/crown_events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crown Events on For The Crown</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	  <atom:link href="/wiki/crown_events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiki: Events History</title>
      <link>/wiki/crown_events/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/crown_events/history/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h2 id=&#34;2020&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;january&#34;&gt;January&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kill the most endermen, each enderman killed rewarded 1 point.&lt;br&gt;
Winner: GodRobin1234 I (Now: Robinoh)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-again&#34;&gt;January again&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kill the most bats, each bat killed rewarded 1 point. Occasinally, a phantom
would spawn in Hazelguard that would reward 5 points when killed.&lt;br&gt;
Winner: Emperor_Axel I&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february&#34;&gt;February&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kill the most endermen. Same as february&lt;br&gt;
Winner: BotulinumToxin I (Now: JulieWoolie)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march&#34;&gt;March&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pinata event. You entered a castle arena and chased a rabbit around with the
goal of punching it. Each time you punched it would give a point and had a
chance of dropping goods like emeralds of diamonds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: Dum_Dum_Playz I&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;april&#34;&gt;April&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PvE event. Fight 3 waves of illagers, pillagers and a ravager in an arena.
Each time you entered the arena you cumulated more points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To keep the waves going, you had to keep control of a capture point within the
castle&amp;rsquo;s center. If you lost the capture point, you&amp;rsquo;d lose the fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: ParanorIV I&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;may&#34;&gt;May&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kill the most endermen, this time with a twist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different end mobs gave different amounts of points. Points were as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enderman: 1pt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Endermite: 5pts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shulker: 15pts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ender Dragon: 500pts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: Monzin I (Now: Mizona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;june&#34;&gt;June&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You were trapped in a small arena with Harold (A villager) while zombies would
spawn in waves and attack him. Your job was to protect Harold from the
zombies. Most waves survived by Harold would win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: HighClaw I (Now banned lmao)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;july&#34;&gt;July&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magmalovania! Players entered a large cave arena in the nether. The event
required players to feed a magma cube with magma slime to grow the slime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hostile mobs would spawn as you fed the magma slime, these mobs attacked you but
also dropped more magma slime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: Monzin II (Now Mizona)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;august&#34;&gt;August&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Players entered the new 1.16 nether world where they were given a list of items
to gather. Points varied by item.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: BotulToxin II (BotulinumToxin, now JulieWoolie)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;september&#34;&gt;September&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Voting event. Players had to vote for the next monarch. There were no rules in
how you got votes, you were allowed to coerce, bribe and cheat. This event was
a failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: mpywrightt I (Now yozakuraaa)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;october&#34;&gt;October&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Custom-generated halloween-themed cave world. Players entered the world and had
to kill zombies, skeletons and other mobs that spawned for points. Points you
earned could also be spent on weapons and armor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: ParanorIV II&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;november&#34;&gt;November&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Event where you raced around a giant mountain covered in obstacles. Fastest won.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: Bablela26 I&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;december&#34;&gt;December&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each event of the year mixed into 1 massive event. Presents would spawn at
random in hazelguard. When you clicked a present, it would either drop some
goodie rewards or send you to a previous event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not all of the years events were possible however, only the following events
were used:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bat event (January)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You were teleported to a shut in cave and had to kill a swarm of bats, each bat
rewarded 1 point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endermen Event (January, May, February)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You were teleported to the end and had to kill endermen, if you killed more
than your previous record, your score went up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pinata (March)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You were teleported to the pinata&amp;rsquo;s arena and had to chase it down and beat it.
If you didn&amp;rsquo;t hit it at all you gained 10 points for being a nice person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Race (November)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You got a ticket to the Race arena and had to get the best time there. The race
event arena&amp;rsquo;s score was factored in later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PvE Arena (April)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You were teleported to the PvE arena and had to fight against illagers and
pillagers. You&amp;rsquo;d lose the fight once you died or the point was captured by the
mobs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protect Harold (June)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You were teleported to a small arena and had to defend the villager Harold from
zombies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: Wout I (Now missing, please find him)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2021&#34;&gt;2021&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;january-1&#34;&gt;January&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spleef event, hosted by PettyGamingHD (Now PettatoGaming).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner: tornnado5 I (Now banned for anti-semitism lmfao)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;february-1&#34;&gt;February&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Randomly generated maze. Quickest to get through the maze won. Every player was
also given 3 bombs when they entered so they could destroy sections of the wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winner; Oweeennnnn I&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;march-2021&#34;&gt;March 2021&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2022&#34;&gt;2022&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023&#34;&gt;2023&lt;/h2&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
